Ugh, God damn it.
This frickin' pisses me off.
I don't get it.
Where'd the damn thing go?
Angelo Katagiri, a .k .a. Angelo.
Known as the sickest, most heinous
criminal in Japanese history.
He continually murdered from the age
of 12, with his final homicide being...
Hey, Milkman!
Watch where you step!
Fouler than dog shit.
In March of 1994,
he came across three
unsuspecting 14-year-old boys,
two of which the monster
proceeded to rape and murder.
You step in something?
Yeah, I suppose I did.
You know what frickin' pisses me off?
People letting their dog
shit in my yard like that!
And I have half a mind to keep
it dumping it in the owner's
pocket tomorrow morning sounds
like fair game to me Excuse me.
I left your milk sitting
right over there later then
Just a sec.
I don't think I've seen
you around here before.
Oh Yeah, i'm just temping for the day.
The third boy came from an extremely
wealthy family so angelo demanded ransom.
That's what led to his arrest.
Well, I hate to nitpick, Temp Guy,
but the safety seal on this
bottle is clearly broken.
Huh? That's so. Take a look.
It's right here, plain as day.
Would you look at that?
I told you it was broken. Yeah.
Sorry for the trouble.
So long.
Thanks again for the milk.
Don't mention it.
Curse that damn bitch!
That one sure is a sharp-eyed vixen.
If only that shrew and her punk
son Josuke had drunk the milk,
my stand aqua necklace would have been
in perfect position to conquer those two.
I can't believe you have more
in there, you little shitter.
When the police finally raided Angelo's
torture den, they found a horrific sight.
The boy had already been murdered.
His genitalia severed and nailed to
a pillar that was standing nearby.
Worthless bastard don't you know how to
pick up after your dog and you just had
to toss your dirty cig on the ground
well you got what you deserved shitface?
Wanna be a pompous asshole?
Then you could swallow my stand
and die like the dirty rat you are!
It's not the beginning of the world,
but it's not the beginning of the world.
But today, I'll see you later on.
I'll see you later on.
Crazy noise is a drum.
The End My hair today, listen.
His stand may not be very strong,
but he can control it
from afar and its ability
to infiltrate bodies is
gonna make things tricky.
Sit tight.
I'll be there soon.
You mean until I get there?
Don't eat or drink anything.
Do you understand?
Stay away from tap water and avoid
the bathroom and shower. Got it.
Can we slow down a bit?
I haven't exactly told
my mom that you're in.
town yet.
She's as tough as they
come, but the thought of Mr.
Joestar can still make her cry.
I think she loves him
even after all this time.
One look at you and she'll
know exactly who you
are.
Hey, Josuke, where'd you get this picture?
It's the Milkman from this morning.
Do you know him?
Josuke, what's wrong?
His stand is already inside.
It was hiding in my mom's coffee
and now it's crawled into her mouth.
Josuke, you there?
Hey, Josuke!
So Josuke, do you want some coffee?
Mmm, that sounds good.
I'll take milk and
sugar if you don't mind.
Milk and sugar it is.
Hey, Josuke, you said
milk and sugar, right?
Yeah.
I'm back, Mr. Jotaro. Still there?
I managed to catch the
little bastard, but... What?
I have no idea what to do now.
How in the hell?
Just be careful.
Angelo's probably spying
on your house as we speak.
Keep your eyes glued to the
stand and I'll be there soon.
Angelo was only able to
survive his execution and
break out of prison because
he had use of a stand.
Still, I don't know the full
extent of his abilities.
Dead ball, sayonara!
Dead ball, game over, sayonara!
Good boy.
You bastard!
I'm gonna smash your prissy face and
rip your smoking hot mom to pieces!
I have to find a way to get that cap
off, or maybe I can break the bottle.
What am I gonna do?
Wait.
Is that…
Higashkata.
I knew that name was familiar.
So, I've stumbled upon
Officer Higashkata's house.
Last time I saw him, I was just twelve.
I know everything there is
to know about you, old man.
Everything!
Freeze.
Josuke, weren't you
supposed to go to class?
Gramps, since when did they let
you take guns home from work?
Since now.
Answer the question.
Yeah, I'm going.
I'm just meeting up with
someone before I leave.
You goober, this is
only a toy gun, my boy.
Had you going, didn't I?
Guess that means the first win of this
week goes to me yeah yeah real funny
you win hmm what's wrong you don't
usually take it on the chin like that fine
and mom left for the day now shouldn't
you be in bed you must be exhausted
for our next story in a gruesome chain
of horrific incidents the death count
has risen to seven in all cases the
victims eyes and ears were disfigured
the incident seems to be isolated to
the town of Mariah but the police aren't
sure whether the trauma is caused by
disease or aggressive behavior i've
encountered this before my gut tells me
these occurrences are undeniably deliberate
i hope it's not as bad
as i think but make no
mistake something wicked's
lurking in this town
grandpa
she's here
I know all of your quirks, Higashikata,
including what you drink after work.
If I recall, your drink of choice
is a nice cognac, isn't it?
Josuke, grab the bottle
and get in the car.
We'll take it where no one
will be able to get hurt.
That's a good idea.
Grandpa.
Just gay he gots guitar
you really blew it kiddo!
You turned your back on the old geezer, and
now he's paid the ultimate price for it.
That's what happens
when you get cocky punk?
You know,
there's nothing quite like the
feeling of bringing a pretentious
bastard crashing down to
earth in a puddle of despair.
That was impressive.
You almost got me.
But almost isn't gonna cut it.
Say goodbye to this world,
cause you're a dead man walking.
I turned away for one second
and he opened the bottle.
Don't worry, though.
I've got this.
I know it doesn't look good,
but after my stand heals him,
it'll be like it never happened.
There. All better.
There's no way that he's…
Just wait, he's going to open his eyes.
My stand has always been
able to heal people.
I've done it so many
times, I've lost track.
I fixed my friend's bones
like it was nothing.
Come on, Grandpa, quit
messing around, okay?
Don't tell me you've already
passed out from last night's shift.
Enough with the jokes!
This isn't funny!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Josuke.
He's healed, right?
Listen, Josuke.
It's said the human organism
must destroy in order to survive.
But your power is an unparalleled
act of compassion in a brutal world.
The problem is, no amount of compassion
or love can bring back the dead.
Not even stands have
that power. I'm sorry.
My grandfather looked after
this town for 35 years.
He never once abandoned his post.
He told me the danger
was lurking as soon as he
heard the news report
about Angelo's return to.
Murder.
I looked into his eyes and saw
a man of honor ready to protect.
Angelo's racked up a high body count.
There are probably more victims out there.
Just waiting to be found.
He kills without motive.
Murdering for the thrill of it.
And this is only the beginning.
I'm certain that he'll keep killing.
But first he'll kill you and your mother.
I'll do it.
I'll take the baton my grandpa left
behind, to protect my mom and the town,
and nothing's going to
get in the way of that.
The End
Eventually, even these
belongings would be discarded.
For despite his daughter's
reluctance to part
with a single one of
her cherished mementos,
his possessions would
never be worn by him again.
I'd like to be there for him, but I'm
sure he needs his privacy right now.
Don't touch anything that's
not from a bottle or can.
We have to be careful.
Where did your mom go?
I asked her to go and visit some
of our relatives after the funeral.
That was good thinking.
She can return after we make Angelo pay.
Before you say anything, I'm doing fine.
I just got a little worked
up hearing his name.
In fact, I've never
been calmer in my life.
Yeah, sure.
Ultimately,
it's your house, so I suppose you can
take out your anger on whatever you want.
By the way, about that
scratch on your lip.
I did that when I punched you, didn't I?
Doesn't your stand possess the
ability to heal your own wounds?
That'd be great, wouldn't it?
But no, it can't.
What if his stand is
somehow able to infiltrate
your body and then tries
to eat its way out of you?
What do you think?
If he gets me, I'm a dead man.
I don't know what you're planning, but
my stand's not going back in that bottle.
You've already played your hand, so I'm
one step ahead of the game, my friend.
Your efforts are futile.
I've got all the time in the world, so
hole up in there as long as you want.
I can wait.
The bastard's been sniffing around
here right under our noses, and still,
he hasn't moved on us in three days.
But why?
What the hell's he waiting for?
It's raining.
Raining? Wait.
Interesting.
I knew you were a weird one, but I
didn't think you'd be a stand user.
No matter.
My moment has finally arrived,
cause this house belongs to me now!
And thanks to this rain,
you're not going anywhere!
By the looks of things, he must
have gotten all this water boiling.
He even turned on the
hot water faucets, too.
To make matters worse,
his stand is in the house.
Turns out he hasn't been waiting
for us to drink the water.
He's been waiting for the rain.
His stand can move anywhere in the rain.
No, it can change
between liquid and vapor.
Josuke, hurry and get
away from the kettle!
He morphed into steam!
Things just got a lot more difficult.
We can't catch him with
the bottle anymore.
For now, stay away from any
steam and protect your lungs.
The priority is getting out of here.
Easier said than done.
I'm not sure we have much of a choice
as far as leaving is concerned.
Of course, Angelo's already put a bunch of
holes in the roof to make his job easier.
Upstairs is no good, and we'll be
sitting ducks if we go outside.
This is just great.
I have to be honest with
you this liquid morphing
stand is way more than
I bargained for plus!
It's really freaky he's a clever bastard
what's so funny the
son of a bitch has?
cornered us hey it's fine mr.
Jotaro my grandpa's murder
has been kind enough to
Turn himself in it's pretty
great don't you think?
Okay it's time to finish
them once and for all
I'm
all ears
Josuke if
you have a plan now's
the time how do we get
out of this get out huh
getting out isn't exactly
what I had in mind?
Breaking out works better.
Come on, this way.
The wall's gonna repair itself.
Good grief.
Well, we blocked the steam at least.
The humidifier!
Josuke!
I'm the winner!
I predicted that you'd break through the
wall and flee into this
room seeking shelter!
Shit too late!
I guess it's like picking
all the right answers.
Or maybe I should compare
it to winning at the races.
Either way,
you can't help but let out a little
giggle when you end up being the victor.
That euphoria is one of the
best feelings in the world.
Chosuke.
Angelo thinks he's won,
but he's got it wrong, Mr.
Jotaro.
Chosuke.
When this battle goes
the way I know it will,
I can promise you I won't feel
like laughing in the least.
Not when I'm fighting a
horrible person like Angelo.
Is that?
You bet it is.
It's kind of gross though.
Sorry about that.
I cut a rubber glove into little
pieces and swallowed it earlier.
Good thinking.
Now we know where Angelo is.
Shit. Shit.
Well, what do you know?
It's Angelo.
Screw the both of you!
Easy now I don't know what you're thinking
but you can't be serious about killing me.
Okay I admit it I escaped that hellhole
called death row and sure I may have been
found guilty Under Japanese law but you
guys have no right to do anything to me
Josuke let's be frank yeah I murdered
your grandpa but that doesn't mean you can
put me to death too if you kill me you'll
You'll end up cursed
just like yours truly!
So back off if you know
what's good for you!
It's rude to point your finger at people.
Didn't your mother ever teach you that?
What the hell did you do to my hand?
You should take solace in the
fact no one's gonna execute you.
Not me, and not this guy either.
We won't be killing you.
Nor will we be turning
you into the police.
Josuke, you handle the rest.
What the hell are you psychotic
bastards planning to do?
Enjoy your eternal penance, Angelo.
Reflect on the life you stole from
my grandpa and all the others!
Here you'll remain for all eternity
in the town my grandpa loved.
Angelo's Rock,
a popular town landmark that's well-known
for being a hotspot for
romantic rendezvous.
For years, it's charmed the residents of
Morioh, despite its disturbing appearance.
Geez, this kid is batshit crazy.
Good grief.
Anytime I need to see your
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taken to a place
with a crystal mind.
A magenta feeling, take a
shelter in the face of my spine.
Like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again.
I'ma move so slightly To the
arms and the lips And the
face of the humic And the
ball that I need to I want to
Come and stand a little bit
closer Breathe in and get a
bit higher You'll never know
what hit you When I get to you.
Ooh I want you I don't know if I
need you Ooh I want you Find help.
Ooh, I want you, I
don't know if I need you
Ooh, I'm trying to find you?